{"data":[{"question":"Mr.Dickson is very tall and big. He needs a ________ raincoat.","a":"large size","b":"short","c":"long and big","d":"long and small","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Because he is both tall and big- his raincoat needs to be both long and big to fit him","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"George is short. He needs ________.","a":"a large size","b":"a medium size","c":"a small size","d":"a big size","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Because he is short- he needs a small one.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Excuse me! ________ you speak English?","a":"Does","b":"Are","c":"Do","d":"Is","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Does: used as an auxiliary ( present simple tense ) before a singular noun in questions .\u00a0\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"________ do you need, Annette?","a":"What","b":"When","c":"Where","d":"Which","answer":"1","explain":"\n- What: used to ask for information or for someone's opinion.\u00a0\n- When (time), where (place), which (thing- to choose).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Mary ________ me the way to Ho Tay lake.","a":"gives","b":"shows","c":"tell","d":"told","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Show(verb): to go with someone and guide them to a place.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"That man brings ________ every morning.","a":"them milk","b":"their milk","c":"milk them","d":"milk for them","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Bring somebody( object form of pronoun) \u00a0something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Take these dishes and bowls ________ the kitchen.","a":"in","b":"on","c":"at","d":"into","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Take something into a place: means you bring it with you and put it in that place","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"You ________ to the seaside this summer.","a":"are going","b":"are going to go","c":"will go","d":"all are correct","answer":"4","explain":"- We use the present continuous when say that you plan to do something in near future","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"I never ________ at home on Sundays.","a":"stay","b":"stays","c":"don't stay","d":"all are correct","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The verb followed by pronoun I would be in plural form\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Listen! My sister ________ in the next room.","a":"is singing","b":"sing","c":"is going to sing","d":"will sing","answer":"1","explain":"\n- We use the present continuous when you say that something happens at the time of speaking","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"}]}